launchbox-app.com 2019-04-04

# PRIVACY POLICY

                                                                                                        Rev. 133C579
State of California
                                           PRIVACY POLICY
                                                 LAUNCHBOX
                                                                                 Version Date: January 25, 2019
 GENERAL
 Unbroken Software, LLC (“Company” or “we” or “us” or “our”) respects the privacy of its users (“user” or
  “you”) that use our website located at https://www.launchbox-app.com, including other media forms, media
  channels, mobile website or mobile application related or connected thereto (collectively, the “Website”).
 The following Company privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) is designed to inform you, as a user of the Website,
  about the types of information that Company may gather about or collect from you in connection with your
  use of the Website. It also is intended to explain the conditions under which Company uses and discloses
  that information, and your rights in relation to that information. Changes to this Privacy Policy are discussed
  at the end of this document. Each time you use the Website, however, the current version of this Privacy
  Policy will apply. Accordingly, each time you use the Website you should check the date of this Privacy
  Policy (which appears at the beginning of this document) and review any changes since the last time you
  used the Website.
 The Website is hosted in the United States of America and is subject to U.S. state and federal law. If you
  are accessing our Website from other jurisdictions, please be advised that you are transferring your
  personal information to us in the United States, and by using our Website, you consent to that transfer and
  use of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. You also agree to abide by the
  applicable laws of applicable states and U.S. federal law concerning your use of the Website and your
  agreements with us. Any persons accessing our Website from any jurisdiction with laws or regulations
  governing the use of the Internet, including personal data collection, use and disclosure, different from those
  of the jurisdictions mentioned above may only use the Website in a manner lawful in their jurisdiction. If
  your use of the Website would be unlawful in your jurisdiction, please do not use the Website.
 BY USING OR ACCESSING THE WEBSITE, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN
  THIS PRIVACY POLICY.
 GATHERING, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF NON-PERSONALLY-IDENTIFYING INFORMATION
 Users of the Website Generally
 “Non-Personally-Identifying Information” is information that, without the aid of additional information, cannot
  be directly associated with a specific person. “Personally-Identifying Information,” by contrast, is information
  such as a name or email address that, without more, can be directly associated with a specific person. Like
  most website operators, Company gathers from users of the Website Non-Personally Identifying Information
  of the sort that Web browsers, depending on their settings, may make available. That information includes
  the user’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, operating system, browser type and the locations of the websites
  the user views right before arriving at, while navigating and immediately after leaving the Website. Although
  such information is not Personally-Identifying Information, it may be possible for Company to determine
Privacy Policy (Rev. 133C579)                                                                              1/7

 from an IP address a user’s Internet service provider and the geographic location of the visitor’s point of
 connectivity as well as other statistical usage data. Company analyzes Non-Personally-Identifying
 Information gathered from users of the Website to help Company better understand how the Website is
 being used. By identifying patterns and trends in usage, Company is able to better design the Website to
 improve users’ experiences, both in terms of content and ease of use. From time to time, Company may
 also release the Non-Personally-Identifying Information gathered from Website users in the aggregate, such
 as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Website.
 Web Cookies
 A “Web Cookie” is a string of information which assigns you a unique identification that a website stores on
 a user’s computer, and that the user’s browser provides to the website each time the user submits a query
 to the website. We use cookies on the Website to keep track of services you have used, to record
 registration information regarding your login name and password, to record your user preferences, to keep
 you logged into the Website and to facilitate purchase procedures. Company also uses Web Cookies to
 track the pages that users visit during each Website session, both to help Company improve users’
 experiences and to help Company understand how the Website is being used. As with other Non-
 Personally-Identifying Information gathered from users of the Website, Company analyzes and discloses in
 aggregated form information gathered using Web Cookies, so as to help Company, its partners and others
 better understand how the Website is being used. COMPANY USERS WHO DO NOT WISH TO HAVE
 WEB COOKIES PLACED ON THEIR COMPUTERS SHOULD SET THEIR BROWSERS TO REFUSE WEB
 COOKIES BEFORE ACCESSING THE WEBSITE, WITH THE UNDERSTANDING THAT CERTAIN
 FEATURES OF THE WEBSITE MAY NOT FUNCTION PROPERLY WITHOUT THE AID OF WEB
 COOKIES. WEBSITE USERS WHO REFUSE WEB COOKIES ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY
 RESULTING LOSS OF FUNCTIONALITY.
 Web Beacons
 A “Web Beacon” is an object that is embedded in a web page or email that is usually invisible to the user
 and allows website operators to check whether a user has viewed a particular web page or an email.
 Company may use Web Beacons on the Website and in emails to count users who have visited particular
 pages, viewed emails and to deliver co-branded services. Web Beacons are not used to access users’
 Personally-Identifying Information. They are a technique Company may use to compile aggregated statistics
 about Website usage. Web Beacons collect only a limited set of information, including a Web Cookie
 number, time and date of a page or email view and a description of the page or email on which the W eb
 Beacon resides. You may not decline Web Beacons. However, they can be rendered ineffective by declining
 all Web Cookies or modifying your browser setting to notify you each time a Web Cookie is tendered,
 permitting you to accept or decline Web Cookies on an individual basis.
 Analytics
 We may use third-party vendors, including Google, who use first-party cookies (such as the Google
 Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize and
 serve ads based on your past activity on the Website, including Google Analytics for Display Advertising.
 The information collected may be used to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the
 popularity of certain content and better understand online activity. If you do not want any information to be
 collected and used by Google Analytics, you can install an opt-out in your web browser
 (https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) and/or opt out from Google Analytics for Display Advertising or
 the Google Display Network by using Google’s Ads Settings (www.google.com/settings/ads).
Privacy Policy (Rev. 133C579)                                                                         2/7

 Aggregated and Non-Personally-Identifying Information
 We may share aggregated and Non-Personally Identifying Information we collect under any of the above
 circumstances. We may also share it with third parties and our affiliate companies to develop and deliver
 targeted advertising on the Website and on websites of third parties. We may combine Non-Personally
 Identifying Information we collect with additional Non-Personally Identifying Information collected from other
 sources. We also may share aggregated information with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and
 investors, for the purpose of conducting general business analysis. For example, we may tell our advertisers
 the number of visitors to the Website and the most popular features or services accessed. This information
 does not contain any Personally-Identifying Information and may be used to develop website content and
 services that we hope you and other users will find of interest and to target content and advertising.
 SOCIAL MEDIA
 We may use hyperlinks on the Website which will redirect you to a social network if you click on the
 respective link. However, when you click on a social plug-in, such as Facebook’s “Like” button, Twitter’s
 “tweet” button or the Google+, that particular social network’s plugin will be activated and your browser will
 directly connect to that provider’s servers. If you do not use these buttons, none of your data will be sent to
 the respective social network’s plugin provider. So for example, when you click on the Facebook’s “Like”
 button on the Website, Facebook will receive your IP address, the browser version and screen resolution,
 and the operating system of the device you have used to access the Website. Settings regarding privacy
 protection can be found on the websites of these social networks and are not within our control.
 COLLECTION, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONALLY-IDENTIFYING INFORMATION
 Website Registration
 As defined above, Personally-Identifying Information is information that can be directly associated with a
 specific person. Company may collect a range of Personally-Identifying Information from and about Website
 users. Much of the Personally-Identifying Information collected by Company about users is information
 provided by users themselves when (1) registering for our service, (2) logging in with social network
 credentials, (3) participating in polls, contests, surveys or other features of our service, or responding to
 offers or advertisements, (4) communicating with us, (5) creating a public profile or (6) signing up to receive
 newsletters. That information may include each user’s name, address, email address and telephone
 number. We also may request information about your interests and activities, your gender, age, date of
 birth, username, hometown and other demographic or relevant information as determined by Company from
 time to time. Users of the Website are under no obligation to provide Company with Personally-Identifying
 Information of any kind, with the caveat that a user’s refusal to do so may prevent the user from using
 certain Website features.
 BY REGISTERING WITH OR USING THE WEBSITE, YOU CONSENT TO THE USE AND DISCLOSURE
 OF YOUR PERSONALLY-IDENTIFYING INFORMATION AS DESCRIBED IN THIS “COLLECTION, USE
 AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONALLY-IDENTIFYING INFORMATION” SECTION.
 Online Postings
 Certain Personally-Identifying Information collected from users may be disclosed as a matter of course as
 a result of your use of the Website. We may provide areas on the Website where you can post reviews and
 other information relating to your activities on the Website. Such postings are governed by our Terms of
 Use. In addition, such postings may appear on other websites or when searches are executed on the subject
Privacy Policy (Rev. 133C579)                                                                           3/7

 of your posting. Also, whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information on publicly-viewable web
 pages, that information will be publicly available and can be collected and used by others. For example, if
 you post your email address, you may receive unsolicited messages. We cannot control who reads your
 posting or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so we encourage you to
 exercise discretion and caution with respect to your personal information. USERS ASSUME ALL
 RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY LOSS OF PRIVACY OR OTHER HARM RESULTING FROM THEIR
 VOLUNTARY DISCLOSURE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION.
 Company Communications
 We may occasionally use your name and email address to send you notifications regarding new services
 offered by the Website that we think you may find valuable. We may also send you service-related
 announcements from time to time through the general operation of the service. Generally, you may opt out
 of such emails by clicking the link at the bottom of the emails, though we reserve the right to send you
 notices about your account, such as service announcements and administrative messages, even if you opt
 out of all voluntary email notifications.
 Company Disclosures
 Company will disclose Personally-Identifying Information under the following circumstances:
      •   By Law or to Protect Rights. When we believe disclosure is appropriate, we may disclose
          Personally-Identifying Information in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent or take other
          action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; to protect and defend the
          rights, property or safety of Company, our users, our employees or others; to comply with applicable
          law or cooperate with law enforcement; to enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements or policies,
          in response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order or a request for
          cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal
          rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases, we may raise
          or waive any legal objection or right available to us.
      •   Marketing Communications. Company may email users about products and services that
          Company believes may be of interest to them. If you wish to opt-out of receiving marketing materials
          from Company, you may do so by following the unsubscribe link in the email communications or
          contacting us using the contact information below.
      •   Third-Party Service Providers. We may share your Personally-Identifying Information, which may
          include your name and contact information (including email address) with our authorized service
          providers that perform certain services on our behalf. These services may include fulfilling orders,
          providing customer service and marketing assistance, performing business and sales analysis,
          supporting the Website’s functionality and supporting contests, sweepstakes, surveys and other
          features offered through the Website. We may also share your name, contact information and credit
          card information with our authorized service providers who process credit card payments. These
          service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but
          are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purpose.
      •   Business Transfers; Bankruptcy. Company reserves the right to transfer all Personally Identifying
          Information in its possession to a successor organization in the event of a merger, acquisition,
          bankruptcy or other sale of all or a portion of Company’s assets. Other than to the extent ordered
Privacy Policy (Rev. 133C579)                                                                         4/7

          by a bankruptcy or other court, the use and disclosure of all transferred Personally-Identifying
          Information will be subject to this Privacy Policy, or to a new privacy policy if you are given notice
          of that new privacy policy and are given an opportunity to affirmatively optout of it. Personally-
          Identifying Information submitted or collected after a transfer, however, may be subject to a new
          privacy policy adopted by the successor organization.
 Changing Personally-Identifying Information; Account Termination
 You may at any time review or change your Personally-Identifying Information by going to your account
 settings (if applicable) or contacting us using the contact information below. Upon your request, we will
 deactivate or delete your account and contact information from our active databases. Such information will
 be deactivated or deleted as soon as practicable based on your account activity and accordance with our
 deactivation policy and applicable law. To make this request, either go to your account settings (if
 applicable) or contact us as provided below. We will retain in our files some Personally-Identifying
 Information to prevent fraud, to troubleshoot problems, to assist with any investigations, to enforce our
 Terms of Use and to comply with legal requirements as is permitted by law. Therefore, you should not
 expect that all your Personally-Identifying Information will be completely removed from our databases in
 response to your requests. Additionally, we keep a history of changed information to investigate suspected
 fraud with your account.
 General Use
 Company uses the Personally-Identifying Information in the file we maintain about you, and other
 information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Website (1) to deliver the products and
 services that you have requested; (2) to manage your account and provide you with customer support; (3)
 to communicate with you by email and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest
 to you either from us, our affiliate companies or other third parties; (4) to develop and display content and
 advertising tailored to your interests on the Website and other sites; (5) to resolve disputes and troubleshoot
 problems; (6) to measure consumer interest in our services; (7) to inform you of updates; (8) to customize
 your experience; (9) to detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; (10) to enforce
 our Terms of Use; and (11) to do as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. At times, we may
 look across multiple users to identify problems. In particular, we may examine your Personally-Identifying
 Information to identify users using multiple user IDs or aliases. We may compare and review your
 Personally-Identifying Information for accuracy and to detect errors and omissions. We may use financial
 information or payment method to process payment for any purchases made on the Website, enroll you in
 the discount, rebate, and other programs in which you elect to participate, to protect against or identify
 possible fraudulent transactions and otherwise as needed to manage our business.
 COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION BY THIRD PARTIES GENERALLY
 Company contractually prohibits its contractors, affiliates, vendors and suppliers from disclosing Personally-
 Identifying Information received from Company, other than in accordance with this Privacy Policy. However,
 third parties are under no obligation to comply with this Privacy Policy with respect to Personally-Identifying
 Information that users provide directly to those third parties, or that those third parties collect for themselves.
 These third parties include advertisers, providers of games, utilities, widgets and a variety of other third-
 party applications accessible through the Website. Company neither owns nor controls the third-party
 websites and applications accessible through the Website. Thus, this Privacy Policy does not apply to
 information provided to or gathered by the third parties that operate them. Before visiting a third party, or
 using a third-party application, whether by means of a link on the Website, directly through the Website or
 otherwise, and before providing any Personally-Identifying Information to any such third party, users should
Privacy Policy (Rev. 133C579)                                                                               5/7

 inform themselves of the privacy policies and practices (if any) of the third party responsible for that website
 or application, and should take those steps necessary to, in those users’ discretion, protect their privacy.
 SECURITY
 We take the security of your Personally-Identifying Information seriously and use reasonable electronic,
 personnel and physical measures to protect it from loss, theft, alteration or misuse. However, please be
 advised that even the best security measures cannot fully eliminate all risks. We cannot guarantee that only
 authorized persons will view your information. We are not responsible for third-party circumvention of any
 privacy settings or security measures.
 We are dedicated to protect all information on the Website as is necessary. However, you are responsible
 for maintaining the confidentiality of your Personally-Identifying Information by keeping your password
 confidential. You should change your password immediately if you believe someone has gained
 unauthorized access to it or your account. If you lose control of your account, you should notify us
 immediately.
 PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES
 Company may, in its sole discretion, change this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any and all changes to
 Company’s Privacy Policy will be reflected on this page and the date new versions are posted will be stated
 at the top of this Privacy Policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information
 that we have about you and your account. Users should regularly check this page for any changes to this
 Privacy Policy. Company will always post new versions of the Privacy Policy on the Website. However,
 Company may, as determined in its discretion, decide to notify users of changes made to this Privacy Policy
 via email or otherwise. Accordingly, it is important that users always maintain and update their contact
 information.
 CHILDREN
 The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA") protects the online privacy of children under 13
 years of age. We do not knowingly collect or maintain Personally-Identifying Information from anyone under
 the age of 13, unless or except as permitted by law. Any person who provides Personally Identifying
 Information through the Website represents to us that he or she is 13 years of age or older. If we learn that
 Personally-Identifying Information has been collected from a user under 13 years of age on or through the
 Website, then we will take the appropriate steps to cause this information to be deleted. If you are the parent
 or legal guardian of a child under 13 who has become a member of the Website or has otherwise transferred
 Personally-Identifying Information to the Website, please contact Company using our contact information
 below to have that child's account terminated and information deleted.
 CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
 California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the "Shine The Light" law, permits our users who are
 California residents to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, information about the
 Personally-Identifying Information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the
 preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of the
 Personally-Identifying Information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with
 which we shared Personally-Identifying Information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are
Privacy Policy (Rev. 133C579)                                                                              6/7

 a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to our
 privacy officer as listed below.
 DO-NOT-TRACK POLICY
 Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems include a Do-Not-Track (“DNT”) feature or setting
 you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities
 monitored and collected. Because there is not yet a common understanding of how to interpret the DNT
 signal, the Website currently does not respond to DNT browser signals or mechanisms.
 CONTACT
 If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact our Privacy Officer at:
 Unbroken Software, LLC
 PO Box 577632
 Modesto, CA 95357
 Email: support@unbrokensoftware.com
 Phone: (815) 762-6244
Privacy Policy (Rev. 133C579)                                                                     7/7

This page intentionally left blank.

                                                         • Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act, which requires
GENERAL INSTRUCTION                                        financial institutions to clearly explain their
WHAT IS A PRIVACY POLICY?                                  information sharing practices and also
                                                           restricts the sharing and use of specific
A Privacy Policy is a document or statement that           financial information.
describes how a company gathers, uses,                   • Health       Insurance      Portability    and
manages, and releases the information of                   Accountability Act (HIPAA) created a
customers or visitors to its website. By accessing         “Privacy Rule” that establishes a national set
the company’s website, users accept to have to             of standards of how health care service
having their information collected and disclosed in        providers can use an individual’s protected
accordance with the company’s Privacy Policy.              health information.
                                                         • Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act
                                                           (COPPA), requires websites that target
WHAT SHOULD BE INCLUDED?
                                                           and/or collect information from children
A simple Privacy Policy will identify the following        under the age of 13 to post a Privacy Policy
basic elements:                                            that     complies      with     the     COPPA
    • Company: The name of the company that                requirements, and also implements certain
      owns the website collecting information from         parental notice and consent requirements.
      its users.
    • Website: The URL address of the                Even if your company or website is not in a
      company’s website that the user will be        jurisdiction that requires a privacy policy, the
      browsing and accessing.                        reach of your website may subject it to the laws of
    • User’s Information: A description of the       other states and countries. For example,
      type of information that the website collects  California, has enacted the California Online
      and discloses.                                 Privacy Protection Act of 2003 (CALOPPA) which
                                                     requires any website collecting personal
    • Collection, Use, and Disclosure: What
                                                     information to have a Privacy Policy posted on its
      information the company will collect , how
                                                     website that is easily accessible to its users. Even
      they will collect and use the information, and
                                                     if your website is not run from California,
      when and to whom they will disclose the
                                                     CALOPPA applies to any website that collects
      information.
                                                     personal information from a California resident.
                                                     Therefore it is likely that your website will be
WHEN IS IT NEEDED?                                   subject to the CALOPPA regulations.
While there is no federal law in the United States
                                                     The European Union has more established laws
requiring that websites establish a Privacy Policy,
                                                     regarding privacy protection, including the Data
many states and most other countries do require
                                                     Protection Directive (95/46/EC) and the E-Privacy
a website that collects and stores any personal
                                                     Directive (2002/58/EC). These directives state
information from its users to have one.
                                                     that personal information of European Union
                                                     residents can only be transferred to countries
In the United States, the Federal Trade
                                                     outside of the European Union that have policies
Commission (FTC) regulates laws and policies
                                                     with an adequate level of protection.
regarding the privacy practices of businesses and
the protection of their customers’ personal
                                                     Therefore, if you are a website that gathers,
information. The FTC also helps to enforce federal
                                                     stores, or uses personal information and data from
laws concerning the privacy of customers’
                                                     clients and users, you should have a Privacy
information, including the following:
                                                     Policy for your website. You also need to make
    • Fair Credit Reporting Act (FCRA), which
                                                     sure that you adhere to the promises and
      limits how companies can obtain and use a
                                                     disclosures set forth in that policy.
      customer’s credit and background reports.

OTHER NAMES                          Privacy Statement, Internet Privacy Policy,
                                     Website Privacy Policy, Privacy Notice, Privacy
A Privacy Policy may also be called: Page, Privacy Information Policy
Privacy      Policy      (Rev.
133C579)
